{
    "id": "2315431e60f54a6196b0aff63a6f1fe9",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The earth is not flat, ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is it",
                "isn't it",
                "is it not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c3e3946c7cf54beab059e908549835af"
        },
        {
            "question": "She isn’t coming, ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "isn't she",
                "is she not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0730ee0396bc4f72b625a49609305333"
        },
        {
            "question": "She called him yesterday, ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did she",
                "didn't she",
                "did she not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6ff4522b6103495891999b87da38ce3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Smoking is injurious to health, ………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is it",
                "isn't it",
                "is it not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2f96db99ec04f3c96cf1a3effcd275e"
        },
        {
            "question": "You met him yesterday, ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did you",
                "didn't you",
                "did you not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "55e825327e6f44519985d15727839901"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let us go for a walk, ………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should we",
                "shall we not",
                "shall we"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "de261f42910b4127a419f941148a5371"
        },
        {
            "question": "She will come, …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will she",
                "won't she",
                "will she not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a07b314431a4282a35f6a3d8d228273"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your parents know this, …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do they",
                "don't they",
                "do they not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b9d0bb2f39414a05b994f05c688c2c30"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody knows the answer, ………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do they",
                "don't they",
                "doesn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3419fc248fc74ae1b43d8d91ef4fd076"
        },
        {
            "question": "She passed the exam, …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did she",
                "didn't she",
                "did she not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ee2d58af595d45c5a644ee61bbf10d94"
        }
    ]
}